Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records Concerning the Yale Vietnam War Memorial
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Secretary's office, Yale University, records concerning the Yale Vietnam War memorial
1974-1978
RU 63
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
The records consist of correspondence, agendas and subject files regarding the Yale Vietnam War memorial.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, agendas and subject files regarding the Yale Vietnam War memorial.
Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Monuments; War memorials; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Working papers and biographical files, 1974-1978; Accession 1992-A-027
  - Vietnam War Memorial working papers, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agenda, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letters and worksheets, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letters, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Memorial dedication meeting, 1978 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Memorial- remarks by President and Chaplain, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam Memorial pamphlet, 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Profiles, Vietnam Memorial pamphlet, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Biographical files
    - Abbott, John 1957E (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Abrams, Lewis H. 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Andrews, Stuart Merrill 1950 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Barschow, William Marcus 1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Boyer, Francis Allard 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Charles Edward, Jr. 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bush, Robert Edward 1953E (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Carpenter, George Whitney 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Emrich, Roger Gene 1963E (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ferguson, Donald Porter 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Foster, Richard McAllister 1923 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Gray, Harold Edwin, Jr. 1953E (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Hayes, Channing Webster, Jr. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Kelley, Kendrick King, III 1966L (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Knapp, Frederic Woodrow 1965 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Lederman, Melvin, M.D. 1952G (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Livingston, Peter Bernard, M.D. 1963M (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Lobit, Hugh Calkins 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - McKellip, Robert, Jr. 1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Marsh, Edward Kettering 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Miller, Marlin McClelland 1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - O'Connel, Richard Martin 1953 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Pershing, Richard Warren 1966 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Schnabolk, Howard Jon 1968Dr (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Shepherd, Richard Dewitt Barlow 1962 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Stillman, Arthur Daniel 1968G (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Swazey, John McArthur 1958 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Van Antwerp, William Meadon, Jr. 1958E (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Warner, Bruce Byerly 1964 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Warner, Stephen Henry 1971L (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Wells, Lloyd Parker III 1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - White, John Clyde, III 1966 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Works, Jonathon Phinney, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 41)